Kamil Bargiel

Founder & CEO at SentiOne

Summary

Founder and CEO of SentiOne - Number One Social Listening and Brand Management.

Serial entrepreneur and startup evangelist in Poland. Public speaker with expertise in Internet and social media. Graduate of CEMS MIM and Warsaw School of Economics. Personally big fan of extreme sports, squash, travelling, italian cuisine and cooking.

Follow me at Twitter: @bargielk

Specialties:

- technology start-ups
- sales
- strategy development
- project management
- marketing & branding
- tech start-ups valuation

Experience

Founder, CEO at SentiOne March 2011 - Present

Deloitte Technology Fast 50 CE Laureate

SentiOne is the First Social Listening and Engagement made for Europe.

Everyday we work with over 500 brands on 29 European markets: Procter&Gamble, McDonald's, Nike, Unilever, Beiersdorf, Tesco, Starcom, Mindshare, Mediacom or Saatchi&Saatchi and many others.

We help global and local brands:

- monitor their brands online
- track social media KPIs
- collect real-time consumer insights
- measure reach of online campaigns
- control their online reputation

- improve online customer care
- identify brand ambassadors
- detect negative mentions
- boost online sales by finding potential leads

We're the only Social Listening Company able to deliver instant local data from 29 European markets:

Germany, Austria, Switzerland, France, Italy, Spain, Netherlands, Belgium, Denmark, Sweden, Norway, Finland, Poland, Russia, Ukraine, Czech Republic, Slovakia, Hungary, Greece, Slovenia, Romania, Lithuania, Latvia, Estonia, Bulgaria, Serbia, Croatia, Montenegro and Bosnia&Herzegovina.

My responsibilities are:

- Strategic Consulting, including business plan & sales strategy development and implementation
- Key Customer Acquisition
- Sales team management, training and recruitment
- Business relations development with Key Customers
- Sales budget preparation and implementation
- Reporting results to the Supervisory Board

CEMS Business Project at Nokia

January 2010 - May 2010 (5 months)

Business project for NOKIA, which aim was to analyse environmental marketing campaigns in the mobile phone industry and other industries.

The main purpose of the project was to describe and analyse environmental marketing campaigns present in broad media by mobile phone manufacturers in Sweden, the UK and Germany. Based on analysing the set of campaigns, a set of recommendations for Nokia's future environmental campaigns has been proposed.

Education

CEMS MIM

M.Sc., International Management, 2009 - 2011

Aalto University

M.Sc., International Management, 2009 - 2010

Warsaw School of Economics

M.Sc., Finance and Accounting, 2005 - 2010

V LO w Bielsku-Białej

A-Level, Mathematics and Computer Science, 2002 - 2005

Honors and Awards

Young Enterpreneur of the Year 2014, Microentrepreneur of the Year 2014, Poland's Most Innovative Project Award for SentiOne, Ernst&Young Financial Challenger, Deloitte Technology Fast 50 CE Laureate, EY Entrepreneur of The Year 2017 Finalist

Kamil Bargiel

Founder & CEO at SentiOne



Contact Kamil on LinkedIn